{
  "theory": {
    "intro": "<par>We know how to calculate a multiplication like <inline-math/>. But what do we do with something like <inline-math/>? The answer is: we can rewrite this by <term>expanding brackets</term>.</par>",
    "rule": "<head>The rule</head><par>If we have a number multiplication, like for instance <inline-math/>, then we can visualize this multiplication using blocks.</par><block-drawing/><par>From this, we see that <inline-math/> can be rewritten to <inline-math/>. Check for yourself: both result into <inline-math/>.</par><par>This works exactly the same if we have an expression like <inline-math/>. Here, <inline-math/>, <inline-math/> and <inline-math/> can be any type of expression, like <inline-math/> or anything similar. We can again visualize this.</par><block-drawing/><par>From this visualization, we see that we may rewrite <inline-math/> to <inline-math/>. We call this <term>expanding the brackets</term>. The accompanying rule is <block-math/> Note that we multiply the factor outside of the brackets (here <inline-math/>) separately with each of the terms inside the brackets (here <inline-math/> and <inline-math/>).</par>",
    "steps": "<head>The steps</head><par>To expand brackets, like for instance with <inline-math/>, take the following steps.</par><list><item><a>Multiply the factor outside of the brackets separately with each term inside the brackets. So <inline-math/> becomes <inline-math/>.</a></item><item><b>For each of the resulting terms, simplify any potential number multiplications. So <inline-math/> becomes <inline-math/> and <inline-math/> becomes <inline-math/>.</b></item><item><c>Also merge any multiplications of equal factors into powers. So <inline-math/> becomes <inline-math/>.</c></item></list><par>The final result <inline-math/> is as easy as you can possibly write it.</par>"
  },
  "meta": {
    "learningGoals": "<par>In this skill you learn to <term>expand brackets</term>. If you see an expression like <inline-math/> you can turn this into <inline-math/>. This includes simplifying the number multiplications (so <inline-math/> becomes <inline-math/>) and turning multiplications of identical factors into powers (so <inline-math/> becomes <inline-math/>).</par>"
  },
  "practice": {
    "basicForm": {
      "mainProblem": "Consider the expression <block-math/> Expand the brackets and simplify the result as much as possible.",
      "step1": {
        "problem": "Take the factor outside of the bracket (here <inline-math/>) and multiply it separately with each of the terms within the brackets (<inline-math/> and <inline-math/>).",
        "solution": "If we set up the two multiplications, keeping a plus in-between, we wind up with <block-math/>"
      },
      "step2": {
        "problem": "Where possible, inside each term, merge products of numbers together into a single factor.",
        "solution": "Both terms have a multiplication of two numbers. We can simplify both of them. This gives us <block-math/>"
      },
      "step3": {
        "problem": "Where possible, inside each term, merge products of equal factors into a power.",
        "solution": "We can turn the multiplication of <inline-math/> with itself into <inline-math/>. This turns the full expression into <block-math/> This is our final answer. In short, <inline-math/>."
      }
    },
    "negativeFactor": {
      "mainProblem": "Consider the expression <block-math/> Expand the brackets and simplify the result as much as possible.",
      "step1": {
        "problem": "Take the factor outside of the bracket (here <inline-math/>) and multiply it separately with each of the terms within the brackets (<inline-math/> and <inline-math/>).",
        "solution": "If we set up the two multiplications, keeping the minus in-between, we wind up with <block-math/>"
      },
      "step2": {
        "problem": "Where possible, inside each term, merge products of numbers together into a single factor.",
        "solution": "Both terms have a multiplication of two numbers. We can simplify both of them. Note that a multiplication of two negative numbers results in a positive number. This gives us <block-math/>"
      },
      "step3": {
        "problem": "Where possible, inside each term, merge products of equal factors into a power.",
        "solution": "We can turn the multiplication of <inline-math/> with <inline-math/> into <inline-math/>. This turns the full expression into <block-math/> This is our final answer. In short, <inline-math/>."
      }
    },
    "multipleTerms": {
      "mainProblem": "Consider the expression <block-math/> Expand the brackets and simplify the result as much as possible.",
      "step1": {
        "problem": "Take the factor outside of the bracket (here <inline-math/>) and multiply it separately with each of the terms within the brackets (<inline-math/>, <inline-math/> and <inline-math/>).",
        "solution": "If we set up the two multiplications, keeping any pluses/minuses in-between, we wind up with <block-math/>"
      },
      "step2": {
        "problem": "Where possible, inside each term, merge products of numbers together into a single factor.",
        "solution": "All three terms have a multiplication of two numbers. We can simplify all of them. This gives us <block-math/>"
      },
      "step3": {
        "problem": "Where possible, inside each term, merge products of equal factors into a power.",
        "solution": "We can turn the multiplication of <inline-math/> with itself into <inline-math/>, and the multiplication of <inline-math/> with <inline-math/> becomes <inline-math/>. This turns the full expression into <block-math/> This is our final answer. In short, <inline-math/>."
      }
    },
    "factorBehind": {
      "mainProblem": "Consider the expression <block-math/> Expand the brackets and simplify the result as much as possible.",
      "step1": {
        "problem": "Take the factor outside of the bracket (here <inline-math/>) and multiply it separately with each of the terms within the brackets (<inline-math/> and <inline-math/>).",
        "solution": "If we set up the two multiplications, keeping the <check><on-true>plus</on-true><on-false>minus</on-false></check> in-between, we wind up with <block-math/>"
      },
      "step2": {
        "problem": "Where possible, inside each term, merge products of numbers together into a single factor.",
        "solution": "Both terms have a multiplication of two numbers. We can simplify both of them. This gives us <block-math/>"
      },
      "step3": {
        "problem": "Where possible, inside each term, merge products of equal factors into a power.",
        "solution": "We can turn the multiplication of <inline-math/> with <inline-math/> into <inline-math/>. This turns the full expression into <block-math/> This is our final answer. In short, <inline-math/>."
      }
    }
  }
}